laneguide.com 2014-11-22

# Lane Guide | Privacy Policy

### Lane Guide | Privacy Policy

This statement was last updated November 7, 2011.

LaneGuide is committed to protecting your privacy. We do require information to provide services that you request, and this privacy statement explains data collection and use in those situations. This privacy statement only applies to LaneGuide.com, LaneGuide.net, LaneCreditorsGuide.com, FindRoutingNumbers.com and CreditUnionRegister.com; it does not apply to any other LaneGuide sites, products or services.  
 Please read the complete LaneGuide.com privacy statement below.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

We will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you personally. Generally, this information is requested when you are purchasing and/or registering LaneGuide products or services. Personal information collected by LaneGuide.com often is limited to e-mail address, personal name, and address, but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested. If you provide a phone number as a contact number, you are authorizing LaneGuide to contact you even if that number is on the Federal Do Not Call list.  
For example: If you choose a service or transaction that requires payment, such as making a purchase at the Online Store of the Web site or subscribing to LaneGuide Online, we will request personal information necessary for billing and shipping, such as: name, address, telephone number, fax number, and credit card number.

When you buy and install a new product, we may ask you to register the product electronically. We keep this registration information on file with any information you've already given us on previous visits to our Web site.  
LaneGuide.com also collects certain information about your computer hardware and software. This information may include: your IP address, browser used, domain name, log information and access time and any referring Web site addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to track general statistics regarding use of LaneGuide.com. LaneGuide.com also collects information about which pages our customers visit or search for within LaneGuide.com.

 LaneGuide.com uses  verification software as subscriber authentication service. When you sign in to this site using Authentix® WebQuota™, you will be asked to provide your e-mail address and a password to sign you in.Use of your Personal Information  
We use your personal information for the following purposes:

\- To deliver services, such as publication updates, software updates, or product that you request or purchase.  
\- To alert you to product upgrades, special offers, pending cancellation, updated information and/or other new services from LaneGuide.  
\- To allow you access to subscription only areas of our site as appropriate.  
\- To allow LaneGuide to fax invoices and renewal offers to any fax number you provide as part of our business relationship with you.

We occasionally contract other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, including packaging or sending U.S. postal mail. 

We will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose.  
LaneGuide may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on LaneGuide or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of LaneGuide; or (c) in case of a force majure.

  **Disclosure of Non-Personal Data**

LaneGuide's primary business activity is an information compiler and data publisher. Information such as company name, address, phone, fax or corporate website, may be included in our publication or database files. Such information is usually of "public record" and part of our usual and customary business practices.

LaneGuide will not disclose your personal information such as personal name, personal email address, credit card information, passwords, products purchased, or visitation information to any third party aside from your listing in the directory.

  **Control of your Personal Information**

When you register, or otherwise give us personal information, LaneGuide.com will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than for the limited exceptions already listed. It will only be used for the purposes stated above.  
LaneGuide.com may send out periodic e-mails or faxes informing you of subscription renewals, issue updates, or releases related to a product or service you ordered, or to confirm you requested a product or service. You will not be able to choose to unsubscribe to these mailings, as they are considered an essential part of the service you have subscribed to and deemed a part of our "business relationship."  
Accessing your Personal Information

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You can review and edit your personal information under Your Account section. You will be asked to enter your email (username) and password before viewing your personal information.  
Some services offered on LaneGuide.com may collect information that is not accessible via the Your Account section. However, in such cases, you can access your personal information by contacting LaneGuide.com as described at the bottom of this statement, or through alternative means of access described by the service. You can change or edit your personal information by contacting one of our Customer Service representatives Monday through Friday, between the hours of 8 a.m. and 5 p.m. PT at 1-800-526-3484.

**Security of your Personal Information**

LaneGuide.com is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access or disclosure. When we transmit sensitive information (such as a credit card number) over the internet, we protect it through the use of encryption technology, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. You can verify the status of the SSL protocol by clicking on the certificate certification link within your browser (e.g., padlock icon) on any secured web page.

We do not store credit card numbers or codes on our servers. We use a bank-approved third-party gateway processor for all online transactions. Further, we do NOT automatically rebill your credit card for subsequent renewals. You will be notified with a renewal invoice at the end of your current subscription period.

**Protection of Children's Personal Information**

LaneGuide.com is a commercial, business to business, site and does not knowingly collect any personal information from children.

**Use of Cookies**  
When a customer visits the site, a cookie may be placed on the customer's machine (if the customer accepts cookies) or is read if the customer has visited the site previously. One use of cookies is to assist in the collection of the site visitation statistics described above.  
LaneGuide may also uses cookies in connection with the use of our Authentix® verification software on the LaneGuide.net Web site. If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies from the LaneGuide.com Web site, may not be able to subscribe or use the service offerings on the site.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
LaneGuide.com will occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the "updated date" at the top of the privacy policy statement.

 **Contact Information:**

LaneGuide welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement, please contact us by e-mail, or U.S. Postal Service.

LaneGuide  
10399 Double R Blvd  
Reno, Nevada 89521  
Last Updated: Thursday, November 7, 2011 - 9:00 am. Pacific Time
